so you're looking to create captions or
subtitles for your YouTube videos well
subtitles is not new to video in fact
most films before 1930 were silent and
use captions with video to really tell
the story now Charlie Chaplin was the
man he didn't even have to say a word
and he was able to really captivate an
audience and in this video I'm going to
show you how to create captions or
subtitles for your YouTube videos and
this can really be powerful because
adding captions can really increase user
engagement and also make that video to
rank a little bit higher in the search
engines let's take a look all right to
add that really important transcription
to your video what you want to do is to
Mouse up to the upper right hand corner
mouse over to video manager and once
you're there you need to select the
video and hit the edit button that you
want to add that transcription to once
you're here you need to see the trend of
the captions tab here click on that and
what happens is YouTube automatically
makes captions and they're not very good
because it has a very difficult time all
the speak a little bit differently and
they do a horrible job at doing it huge
task and so what we need to do is help
them out so the first thing is is you
actually have a script that you read
from you can actually just upload the
file just click this right here and just
upload the file really easy it will just
sync and it's super easy now if you
don't you can go ahead and hit the
transcribe and sync now this is where
it's really cool and YouTube's making it
really easy for all of us to transcribe
our videos to make you the search
engines easier to to know what we're
saying so the great thing about it is
you can actually have the video start
playing take a few minutes and leave my
office get away from the game and as you
start typing it stops the video tickle
justtake now the great thing about it
too is if you hit shift and the left
arrow it takes it back five seconds and
then also I'm going to just pause it
here also you can hit shift + the space
key and it actually pauses it so I'm
going to go ahead and and go through it
and this is where you can go around and
play with it a little bit but I'm going
to go ahead and do the transcription
here real quick okay now when you have
the whole video transcribed all you need
to do now is click the sync button and
it's right here this blue button here
what it's doing it's syncing what you
typed with what you're saying okay you
actually have two active tracks now that
it's synced we need to get rid of the
automatic captions and to do that just
click on it come up here to actions and
hit disable and click over here on
active tracks and I want to show you
here so let's let me just show you what
it does here so let's go ahead and hit
this and hit play wanted to take a few
minutes and leave my office get away
from the computer and take a you know
just take a little jaunt this is just a
few blocks so you can see how great it
is it just works out perfectly